(水月)ひとつ聞いてもいいかな。
(サスケ)なんだ？
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
どうして 仲間を集めるの？
Why are you gathering men?
オレには目的がある。
I have a goal...
その目的に近づくには
小隊のほうが効率がいい。
And I have a better chance of
achieving it with a small platoon.
大蛇丸に近づいたときから➡
Ever since I approached Orochimaru,
this moment is all I've thought about,
こうなったときのことを考え➡
力のある忍を
前もって選抜しておいた。
and I've been pre-selecting
highly skilled Ninja.
へえ。
Oh...?
けど だったら 香燐を
選ぶことはないと思うけどね。
So...why would you choose Karin?
アイツは ボクと違って
大蛇丸の部下だよ。
Unlike me,
she's a follower of Orochimaru...
大蛇丸に狩り集められた実験体を
ぶち込んだ➡
The warden of the southern hideout
where Orochimaru kept
his test subjects locked up.
南のアジトの看守殿だ。
それに
大蛇丸の命令だとか言って➡
After claiming to be
under Orochimaru's orders,
アイツには 何度も
体をいじくられたよ。
she tinkered with
my body countless times.
第一
あの性格が好きになれない。
Besides, her personality turns me off.
確かに 扱いやすそうな強い忍は
他にいくらでもいた。
Granted, there were other strong Ninja
I could have swayed.
しかし ヤツは他にない
特別な能力を持っている。
But she has a special power
no one else possesses.
まあ それは認めるけどね。
Well... I'll admit that.
(香燐)いい香り。
A nice smell...and a bad odor.
それと イヤなにおい。
ずいぶんと警備が手薄なアジトだね。
There's hardly any security
in this hideout.
塀くらい建てればいいのに。
They should at least build a fence.
アイツがここをおさめているんだ
必要ないだろう。
She has this place under control.
There's no need.
にしても静かすぎないかな。
Still, it's too quiet.
大蛇丸が死んだという
ウワサが届いていても➡
You'd think that word of
Orochimaru's death
had already reached this place...
おかしくないのにさ。
え？
キミだって持ってるっしょ。
You have one too.
そっちのほうがあってる。
That one is more suitable.
開けゴマ！
Open sesame!
なあやっぱり オレは思うんだよ
あの噂は 本当だったんじゃ？
Say, I've been thinking.
That rumor must be true--
やめろ！ そいつを口にした者が
どうなってきたか…。
Shut up!
You know what happened to
the others who brought that up...
ああ そうだな。
Yeah...
you're right...
Oh, damn it...
まずい まずい！
あれは うちはサスケだ！
That's Sasuke Uchiha!
どうして こんなところへ？
What's he doing in a place like this?
もう ずいぶん前になるぜ
大蛇丸と ヤツが来たのは。
It's been quite a while
since he came here with Orochimaru.
そうだよ なんで大蛇丸と来ない？
Yeah, why didn't he come
with Orochimaru?
He's with a guy
we've never seen before...
あんな見たこともねえヤツと…。
あの噂は 本当かもしれんぞ！
Maybe that rumor is true...!
About Orochimaru being dead.
大蛇丸が死んだって！
そうか サスケが大蛇丸を
倒したんだよ！
That's it!
Sasuke must've killed Orochimaru!
それで オレたちを
解放しに来てくれたんだぜ！
And he's come to free us all!
バーカ そんなこと
あるわけねえだろ。
Idiot. Like that'll ever happen!
だいたい 大蛇丸が
やられるわけがない。
Besides, Orochimaru would
never get killed.
(香燐)やっぱり アンタか サスケ。
So it's you, after all...Sasuke.
Guardian of the Iron Wall
サスケ アンタがここへ
１人で来たってことは➡
Sasuke...
The fact that you're here alone
must mean that the rumors were true.
あの噂は 本当だったみたいだな。
ひどいな ボクもいるってのに。
Geez, that's mean. I'm here too.
で ここに何の用だ？
And? What brings you here?
サスケが キミに話があるんだってさ。
Sasuke has something
to discuss with you.
立ち話もなんだから
別部屋に案内してくれないかな？
We can't stand out here and talk,
so take us inside, will you?
久しぶりに歩いたら
ヘトヘトでね。
It's been so long since I've walked...
I'm exhausted.
なんだよ 話って。
What do you want to talk about?
だから 立ち話もなんだからって
言ってるんだけどね 香燐。
I said let's not stand out here, Karin.
Although I know
you're totally ignoring me.
ボクは キミの眼中にないってことは
わかってるけどさ。
フン！
Humph!
イヤな感じ。
何言ってんの お前？
You disgust me.
What'd you say?
いいかげんにしろ 香燐。
部屋に案内しろ。
Cut it out, Karin. Take us inside.
わかったわよ。
Fine.
香燐 ついてこい
お前が必要だ。
Karin, follow me. I need you.
はあ？ なんで お前なんかに？
Huh?! Why would I follow you?
I'm under orders to oversee this place!
ウチは ここを任されてんだよ。
大蛇丸は もういない。
Orochimaru is already gone.
What about the prisoners here?
捕まえてるヤツらは
どうすんだよ。
そういやさ アイツらずいぶんと
おとなしかったね。
Speaking of prisoners,
they were awfully quiet.
大蛇丸が死んだって噂
このアジトにも届いてたろ？
Have the rumors about
Orochimaru's death reached them?
前に ここに来たときよりも
囚人の数が微妙に減ってる。
The number of prisoners has slightly
lessened since I came here last.
それと入り口前の庭に➡
Also, there are signs of recent digging
in the grounds in front of the entrance.
最近 穴でも掘ったような
形跡がいくつかあった。
香燐 お前の頭脳をもってすれば➡
Karin, with that sharp intellect,
information control must be your forte.
情報統制などお手の物だろ。
そっか 大蛇丸が死んだという
ウワサが囚人たちに流れ➡
I get it.
Rumors about Orochimaru's death
began spreading among the prisoners,
so in order to avoid a riot,
Karin has been wisely taking action...
暴動に発展しないように香燐が
うまく立ち回っていた。
ということか。
Is that it?
おい あのウワサ知ってるか？
Hey, do you know about
that rumor?
Yeah, I know.
About Orochimaru being killed, right?
ああ 知ってる知ってる。
大蛇丸が 死んだって話だろ。
ああ。
Yeah.
You planted a spy among the inmates
(水月)檻の中にスパイを紛れ込ませ➡
ちょっとでも大蛇丸の
ウワサをするものがいれば…。
and if anyone began gossiping
about Orochimaru...
Karin, it's your cautious nature which
maintained order in the prison.
香燐 お前のその慎重さが➡
このアジトの秩序を保った。
というより お前自身を救った。
Or rather...kept you alive.
嫌な言い方するんじゃないよ！
You'd better stop talking like that!
さすが大蛇丸仕込みの女だ。
You've been trained by Orochimaru,
all right. Man, you're scary.
こええ。 オレたちが来たことも
とっくに感づいてたんだろうな。
You probably sensed
our presence long ago.
下手すれば 殺されてたかも
しれないってことだ。
You could've even killed us by now.
アンタ１人だったらね。
If you were alone.
サスケだったらいいってのかよ。
But not Sasuke?
そんなこと 言ってない。
サスケはいわば同僚だ。
I didn't say that!
Sasuke is a colleague.
それに
ウワサの真偽を確かめたかった。
I wanted to see if
the rumors were true...
サスケが大蛇丸を
やったっていうウワサをね。
that Sasuke killed Orochimaru.
オレがやった。
何簡単に言ってんだよ！
I did kill him.
How can you say that so casually?!
水月 このアジトに捕らえられてる
ヤツらを 全員解放しろ。
Suigetsu... Release everyone
who is held prisoner here.
Wha--?!
な…。
はぁ～。
Geez... You always
order people around.
《相変わらず命令口調だな》
勝手なことすんじゃねえよ！
You can't just come here
and take over!
私がどんだけ
苦労してここをしめてきたか。
You don't know what it took
to keep things in order here...
囚人がいなけりゃ
監視役も必要なくなるわけだ。
Without prisoners,
there won't be any need for a warden.
もう一度言う。
オレについて来い 香燐。
I'll say it once more.
Come with me, Karin.
What'll you do?
どうする？
Well, anyway,
I'll go and release the prisoners.
じゃあ 囚人たちを
解放しに行って来る。
I refuse! Besides...
お断りだね！ だいたい
アンタについて行く義理はないだろ。
I'm under no obligation to follow you!
ふ～ん。
仕方ない。
お前がそこまで嫌がるのなら➡
Too bad...
Since you seem dead set against it,
I'll just ask someone else.
他を当たろう。
やっぱりだぜ！ うちはサスケが
大蛇丸を倒したというのは。
I knew it!
The rumors that Sasuke Uchiha
brought down Orochimaru were true!
ホントだったのか。
ああ そうだよ。
Yeah, it's true.
捕まってるオレたちは どうなる？
What'll happen to those of us in here?
もちろん自由だよ。
Of course, you're free to go.
ホ ホントか？
A-Are you sure?!
Yeah... I was once imprisoned too.
But as you can see, I'm free.
ああ。 ボクだって同じ
捕らわれの身だった。
でも こうして外にいるだろ。
今からカギを開けるよ。
I'm going to unlock the cells.
Before that, I have one favor to ask.
ただ その前に➡
みんなに
ひとつだけお願いがあるんだ。
何だ!? 何でも言ってくれ！
What is it?! Ask us anything!
そうだな…。 大蛇丸を倒し➡
Well...
The one who defeated Orochimaru
and gave us our freedom is Sasuke.
ボクたちの自由を
取り戻してくれたのはサスケだ。
外に出たら そのことを
言い広めてくれ。
When you're out,
spread the word to everyone...
この世に
安定と平和をもたらす男が➡
A man has appeared who will
bring peace and tranquility to this world.
現れたとね。
行く！
I'm coming.
あっ…。
サスケがぁ
どうしてもって言うなら➡
Since you're so adamant...
ついてってやるよ！
I'll go with you.
どういうことだ？
What's this?
That was a quick change of heart.
心変わりが早いな。
よく考えたらぁ➡
After thinking it over,
見張りも
あきちゃってたところだし。
I realized I'm tired of
guarding this place.
(水月)なかからカギを… あの女。
It's locked from the inside...
That woman!
フンッ！
水月か…。
That's Suigetsu.
邪魔者はほっといて！
Let's forget about that nuisance,
okay, Sasuke?
ねっ サスケ。
お前 少しはなれろ。
You... Don't get so close.
ねぇ どうせなら
ウチとサスケだけでいいんじゃない？
Look...what's wrong with
just you and me?
水月なんていらないだろ あれ。
We don't need a guy like...Suigetsu.
お前のその小ズルさと用心深さ➡
Your cunning and sense of caution...
そして何より
そのチャクラを感じる能力。
and especially your power
to sense Chakra...
お前は使えるとわかっていた。
From the moment I met you,
I knew I could use you.
初めて会ったあのときから。
《そう… あのとき…》
Yes...that time...
((大蛇丸様から言われて来た。
Lord Orochimaru sent me here.
To assist you, Sasuke Uchiha.
うちはサスケ アンタを手伝えと。
２時間前にアジトから
118名の実験体が脱走した。
Two hours ago, 118 test subjects
escaped from the hideout.
時間的にみて
全員 まだこの森のなかにいる。
Judging from the time,
they are all still in this forest.
捕獲命令は
生死を問わずと聞いている。
I understand that this order
is to capture them dead or alive.
ああ。
Yeah.
Well then, let's begin.
だったら とっとと始めるよ。
《50… 60…。
50, 60...
70… 80… 90… 100》
70...80...90...100!
見つけた。
Found them!
I'll start with the ones hiding
closest to us.
まずは
近場で潜んでるヤツから いくよ。
後方50メートルに １人。
前方10時の方向に ４人。
There's one fifty meters behind us.
And four more in front of us
at ten o'clock.
早い！
So fast!
ついてこられるか？
任務だからな。
Can you keep up?
It's my duty.
香燐 オレの目となれ。
Karin, become my eyes.
うっ… ウチに命令するな！
D-Don't give me orders!
１時半の方向に潜んでるのが３人。
Three are hiding over at 1:30.
さらに そこから
９時の方向に待ち伏せ５人。
And from that point, at nine o'clock,
there are five more waiting
to ambush us.
うっ…。
何人だ？
これで 84。
How many?
This one makes 84.
サスケ どうして殺さない？
Sasuke, why don't you kill them?
お前 ぬるいな。
You're so lenient.
オレが殺したいのは
たったひとりだけだ。
There's only one man
I have a desire to kill.
《うっ… 何？
コイツの… このチャクラ…》
Wh-What...?!
This guy's...Chakra...!
《コイツ… かっけえ…》
This guy...is cool!
香燐。
Karin!
香燐！
ウチのために… お前…。
You did that...for me?
お前を失えば すべての実験体を
捕らえることは困難になる。
If I were to lose you, capturing
the escapees would become difficult.
わかってる。
I know!
《あのとき…》
At that moment...
《ウチは サスケに… サスケに…》
I... Sasuke... Sasuke, I...
ああ… 刃こぼれしてないかな。
Hope my blade isn't chipped...
さあ いこうよ サスケ。
香燐は ダメだったんだろう？
Let's go, Sasuke.
Karin turned you down, didn't she?
いや どうやら ついてくるようだ。
No. It seems she's coming.
だ… 誰が行くっつった!?
Wh-Who said I'm coming?!
I just... I just happened to be
going in the same direction.
ウチは たま… たまたま
一緒に行方が同じだった。
行くだけ… だけで…。
That's all, nothing else...!
だから… その…。
へえ～ なら ちょうどいいね。
途中まで一緒に行こうよ。
Oh, how nice.
Then we can travel together partway.
ああ… 途中までな。
Yeah, just part of the way!
(水月)さて次は重吾だね。
All right... Next is Jugo.
なに！
重吾のところへ行くだって!?
What? You're going to see Jugo?
途中まで一緒なだけなキミには
関係ないでしょう。
That shouldn't concern you
since you're just coming
with us part of the way.
関係ないけど それがどうした！
やんのか コラ！
Sure, I could care less,
but what's wrong with asking?
Wanna make something of it,
you jerk?!
行くぞ。
Let's go!
あっ… ああ。
Y-Yeah...
行ってやる！
I'll go!
《香燐 : うちはサスケ…
そのクールな顔もいいけれど…》
Sasuke Uchiha...
He always looks so calm and cool...
《この感じ ゾクゾクする…。
This feeling...is exciting.
今まで何百 何千と出会った中で
最高のチャクラ… グッとくる～！
Of the hundreds, the thousands
I've encountered,
his Chakra is the best...
It grabs you!
それに比べて…》
Compared with that...
ん？ 何だよ？
What?!
アンタのチャクラ 苦手だわ。
Your Chakra...bothers me.
あぁ？
Huh?
ボクのほうこそ！
I could say the same about yours.
いや やっぱ女…
やっぱ女がいいな。
No, a woman...
A woman is nice... No, wait.
いや 待てよ。
やっぱ男か… やっぱ男がいいか。
A guy? I guess a guy is better...
いや やっぱ女か…？
No... A woman...?
女が…。
A woman... No...
いや それよりも 男…。
Maybe a guy...
We have to keep walking?
I'm exhausted.
We're about to go to
the northern hideout.
If you're acting like that, you'll be killed
the moment you arrive there.
I didn't realize the place
is so dangerous.
Yeah, the northern hideout is
no ordinary hideout.
What do you mean by that?
The place is
a human experiment facility.
Intolerably bad monsters were
created there and kept under restraint.
Next time:
"Jugo of the Northern Hideout"
(ナルト)うずまきナルトの
『ぐるぐるラジオ』！
Naruto Uzumaki's Swirling Radio!
Our guest today is...
本日のゲストは！
Hello, I'm Kakashi Hatake.
(カカシ)どうも！ はたけカカシです。
それでは さっそく。
リハのときさ 勝手なアドリブ入れるの
ホント やめてくんねえかな。
な… なんだと!? オレは
現場の空気を和ませようとだな！
そのわりには 楽しそうだよな。
そ… そういう演技をしてるんだ。
へぇ～ まあ いいや。
ここで お便りを。
ラジオネーム 鳥獣戯画さん。
「カカシ先生のあだ名を
考えてみたのですが➡
エロハリネズミなんてどうですか？」。
オレの威厳が…。
えっと 続いては
ラジオネーム キラキラ乙女さん。
「ズバリ 結婚しないんですか？
それと集合時間に遅れてくるクセ
あれ ホント迷惑です。
あと 私たちの前で
いかがわしい本を読まないで。
はっきり言って
すっげぇセクハラです」。
あれ？ カカシ先生どうしたの？
カカシ先生！ また来てくれるかな？
二度と来るかぁ～！
(ナツ)この先にいるエルザを倒し➡
俺は Ｓ級魔導士になるんだ！
誰かいるぞ。
(ハッピー)誰だろう？
(２人)あぁ…。